4/16/2021 My Cv

# **OLALERE PRECIOUS MONJOLAOLUWA**

No D16, Oke-Andi, Sango, Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria. 09027147282 | olalereprecious14@yahoo.com

# **OBJECTIVE**

I am an amiable and ardent librarian dedicated to serving people by providing assistance in information retrieval and research techniques. I am passionate about promoting literacy by educating people on information literacy. I have strong writing skills and excellent oral communication skills which has helped me to answer patrons questions at the information desk.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Nigeria Stored Product Research Institute, Ilorin, Kwara State.

April 2019 - Septemeber 2019

Librarian intern

- Performed digital research using databases such as TEAL and AGORA.
- Answered patrons' questions and assisted in finding materials requested.
- Sourced materials that met current needs, drove curiosity and supported learning.
- Handled multitude of daily tasks, including facility maintenance and security in support of staff members.
- Assisted patrons in regards to library's computer system and gave instructions for logging onto the internet.
- Evaluated appropriateness of book(s) based on patron needs.
- Guided researchers who were seeking information by directing them to specific library databases, unique collections, and other reference materials.

#### Zuri Training.

March 2021 - till date

Frontend developer intern

- Currently interning at Zuri training as a frontend developer.
- Worked on different Task using HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT.

# **EDUCATION**

• University of Ilorin, Ilorin, Kwara State. 2016-2020

Bsc. Library and Information Science

 Unilorin Secondary School, P.M.B 1515, Ilorin, Kwara State. 2010-2016
Senior School Certificate

127.0.0.1:5501/index.html 1/2

4/16/2021 My Cv

 Lower Niger River Basin Nursery. 2002-2010
Certificate of Primary Education

## **SKILLS**

- A naturally hospitable and friendly personality which is essential in project-oriented job.
- Posses solid computer skills.
- Outstanding customer service skills.
- Excellent Research skills.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS**

- Certificate of Merit as the Drama Coordinator of the Fellowship of Christian Student Association of Unilorin Secondary School, Ilorin, Kwara State – July 2015–July 2016
- Certificate of Merit in French Language, Agricultural Science, Christian Religious Studies, Yoruba at Unilorin Secondary School, Ilorin, Kwara State- 2013
- Certificate of Merit in Agricultural Science, at Unilorin Secondary School, Ilorin, Kwara State- 2016

127.0.0.1:5501/index.html 2/2